To summarize this video, register allocation is one of the most important jobs that a compiler
综上所述，寄存器分配是编译器最重要的工作之一
performs. And it's really, these days they must have an any kind of reasonable
执行。而且真的，这些天他们肯定有一种任何一种合情合理的
production compiler. And, the reason you need it is because the inter-media
生产编译器。而且，你需要它的原因是因为中间媒体
code just generally uses too many temporaries. We're allowed to be a little
代码通常只是使用了太多的临时函数。我们被允许有一点
bit sloppy with intermediate code precisely because we have good register allocation
中间代码的位马虎正是因为我们有很好的寄存器分配
algorithms. And the other reason, registers are just a very important
算法。另一个原因是，寄存器是非常重要的
resource in making good user registers. Having some procedure for making
做好用户注册所需的资源。有一些制作过程
efficient use of the registers. Leads to much, much better code in the end,
有效利用寄存器。最终会产生更好的代码，
much more efficient code. Now. The register allocation algorithm I described
更高效的代码。现在。我描述的寄存器分配算法
here is really targeted at risk machine. So, for risk machine reduce instruction set
这里真正针对的是风险机器。因此，对于风险机器缩减指令集
computer what kind of machine. You can pretty much take the register allocation algorithm
电脑是什么样的机器。您几乎可以采用寄存器分配算法
that I described and if any for those machines it would work out of the box.
这是我描述的，如果那些机器有的话，它可以开箱即用。
CISC machines - which stands for complex instructions for computers - often
CISC机器-代表计算机的复杂指令-通常
have restrictions on how the register can be used. Certain operation can only work with
对如何使用寄存器有限制。某些操作只能与
certain registers. You may have register to different sizes that can only
某些寄存器。您可能有不同大小的注册，只能
hold certain values. And so it becomes more complicated to register allocation for
保持一定的价值观。因此，为其分配寄存器变得更加复杂
such machines. What people have done is to adapt the graph coloring procedure that
这样的机器。人们所做的是修改图形着色过程，
I described here. So, the basic idea is exactly the same and you would recognize
我在这里描述过。所以，基本概念是完全相同的，你会认识到
those algorithms is being primarily the graph color algorithms that
这些算法主要是图形颜色算法，
we discussed. There are just additional. Steps in those algorithms and places where
我们讨论过。只有一些额外的。这些算法和位置中的步骤
the particular constraints are what registers can be used have to be observed.
具体的约束是必须观察可以使用什么寄存器。